superbpaper.com 2019-03-17

# Privacy Policy | SuperbPaper.com

There is a portion of obligatory personal information, which we must receive from the client before working on the first order. We require personal information such as your name, contact phone number, email address and country of residence.

The information we collect may be used for the following purposes:

  * To make a personal account on SuperbPaper.com. If a client is registered in our system, it is easier to track his/her orders and record the preferences of the client. We can also attend to you quickly and efficiently.
  * To change our website according to clients’ preferences and needs. We may receiveour clients’ comments and feedback about our website or company that we need to take into consideration.
  * To get in touch with clients. It is crucial for our customer support department to have our clients’ contact information because such personal information will allow us to contact the client immediately in case of an emergency. As returning clients, you don't have to give us all your personal details again and again. You just have to log in, fill the order form, and your order will be registered in our system.

**Information Security**

All information we get from our clients is stored safely on our server. We are very concerned with the issue of personal information security and that is why we have invested into getting reliable protection systems. Both general and private data obtained from our clients will be protected via a Secure Socket Layer (SSL) system. To process a payment, we only use verified payment processors.No client’s information will be stored on the server of the payment processors.

**Cookies Usage**

Small text fragments that are transferred from our server to our clients’computers are called cookies. Cookies are placed on a computer’s hard drive only if the client permits this action. By using cookie files, we can monitor and track client’s activities on our site and receive additional information, like the type of browser or type of connected device.

Thanks to cookies, we can receive valuable information that allows us to better our service and website. We can stop using your browser’s cookies after a specific request from you.

**Giving Information to Third Parties**

We guarantee 100% protection of client’s personal information and by no means do we share personal information of our clients with a third party or organization. Access to the database containing our clients’ personal information will be given to staffs that are authorized for the sole purpose of processing orders. Only in somerare and individual cases, we may have to reveal personal information, for instance: correspondence to law, strengthening company policies or protecting the company's rights.

We have a right to disclose non-personal information for marketing purposes or arranging surveys.

**Online Children Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We perform our services according to the COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act) standards. This just means that our company is not permitted to sell or offer services to individuals less than 13 years of age. Any person over the age of 13 is allowed to use our services.

The following Privacy Policy refers to data gathered online only. Every other personal data, which is collected offline, is not included in this Privacy Policy, and our company will not bear responsibility.

Users should read the Terms and Conditions described on this website thoroughly so they may be adequately informed about their rights.

By using our services, individuals automatically accept our policies and rules that are presented on this website.
